Resume (EN) / Frontend Developer



Name: Ivan

Surname: Pankov

Middle name: Eduardovich Birth date: 21 august 1993

Citizenship: Russia

Family status: Not married, No children

City: Moscow / Obninsk (Russia)

Phone: +7 (960) 524 57 42 Email: hypotenuse@yandex.ru

Github: https://github.com/hypotenuse

Facebook:

https://www.facebook.com/hypotenuse2

Goal

This resume primarily written for employers. If you need a Frontend Developer you can view my resume. If you need more information about me or my experience you can always write me on my email written above or use Facebook. I also glad for any suggestions you have (full-time work, interesting projects, etc)

Education

(2012 - 2015)

Obninsk Institute for Nuclear Power Engineering. Branch of MEPhI. Faculty of Cybernetics / Department of information systems / Bachelor course

Experience

07.2015 - 10.2016 (1 year 3 months)	tovarovoz.com (internet-shop) Worked as a Frontend Developer
	Technology stack: Backend: - Scala (PL) + Play Scala Framework - PostgreSQL (DB) Frontend: - Native JavaScript - Angular 1 - Angular Bootstrap UI - Bootstrap - Plain CSS without preprocessors
	Responsibilities: - Support and development of UI logic - Existing solutions integration - Interaction with the server part via REST API - Bugfixing
	Repository: https://github.com/hypotenuse/hypotenus e.inetshop
04.2015 - 06.2015 (2 months)	efantz.com Worked as a Frontend Developer
	Technology stack: Backend: PHP (Laravel) Frontend: Native JavaScript + Angular 1
	Responsibilities: - Reorganize application fully written on PHP as SPA using Angular 1 - Parsing of esports.smitegame.com - Implement authorization logic in Angular 1
	Repositories: https://github.com/hypotenuse/hypotenus e.esg https://github.com/hypotenuse/hypotenus e.efantz

Skills & Technological stack

- Native JavaScript (ES5 / ES6 / ES7+ standards)
- Object Oriented / Functional / Asynchronous Programming
- Babel
- Angular 1.x.x
- React / React + Redux
- Webpack 1 / Webpack 2 / Webpack 3
- HTML5 / CSS / SASS (SCSS)
- Node.js / NPM / Express framework
- MongoDB / MySQL (bad)
- Git / Github / Gitlab
- Http(s) / Ws(s) Protocols

Languages

- English
- Russian

Personal Qualities

- Write neat and quality code
- Understand code not written by me
- Strive to apply known development patterns and follow DRY principles
- Strive to work in IT area as a software developer / engineer
- Like analytical geometry!